So now that we have our getMetricMetaInfo function all set up,
我们已经设置好了 getMetricMetaInfo 函数
let's go ahead and use it.
我们来使用该函数吧
This brings us to building our very first component.
我们将构建首个组件
So let's go ahead and make a new folder here. We'll call it components.
在这里新建一个文件夹 命名为 components
And inside of here,
并在里面
let's create an AddEntry.js file.
创建一个 AddEntry.js 文件
And so we are going to import React from React.
从 React 导入 React
Let's also grab components,
并获取组件
as we've seen just in normal react on the web.
就像在网络平台上的普通 react 中一样
But now what we want to do,
但是现在
is let's go ahead and grab,
我们将从 react-native
View and Text from React Native and then let's go ahead
获取 View 和 Text
and grab that getMetricMetaInfo function that we just barely built,
然后获取我们刚刚构建的 getMetricMetaInfo 函数
that lives inside of utils/helpers and
位于 utils/helpers
then now our very first to React Native component is going to be this AddEntry component,
这个 AddEntry 组件将是我们的首个 React Native 组件
which is going to extend components.
扩展自 Component
And for now, let's just go ahead and return a UI
现在返回一个 UI
that has a view and then we will give it a text of AddEntry,
其中有一个 View 里面包含文本“Add Entry”
just so we know that it's working.
确保该组件能正常运行
And then now inside of our app file,
转到 App.js 文件
first let's go ahead and
首先删除
delete a lot of the stuff that we're not going to be using for right now.
暂时不会用到的大量内容
So let's delete all of this,
删掉它们
as well as the style.
以及样式
And then we can delete both of these.
删掉它俩
And then to be controversial let's delete the semi colons.
然后删掉这些有争议的分号
Alright, so now what I want to do real quick is let's import
现在我将快速地
that AddEntry component that we just made.
导入刚刚创建的 AddEntry 组件
It's going to be coming from component/AddEntry and then now let's render it.
来自于 components/AddEntry 现在渲染它
So what we should see if everything's working correctly.
我们应该能看到一切是否正常
Looks like we have a typo here.
似乎这里有个错别字
So, unexpected token 142 on helper's.
提示 helpers 中的第 142 行有问题
So util/helpers 142, let's unminimize this,
依次转到 utils helpers 第 142 行 收起这些内容
and down here I think what our issue is,
在这里可以看到问题是什么
is we have type here instead of typeof.
我们输入的是 type 而不是 typeof
Type obviously isn't a thing.
type 明显不对
So now go ahead and see if this works.
现在看看是否能正常运行
Typically with iOS you have to refresh it.
通常 对于 iOS 平台 需要刷新下
So you'll notice now up here,
现在可以在顶部看到
behind the status bar, we have this text.
在状态栏后面有一个文本
So the status bar is hiding are our AddEntry text but eventually we'll fix that.
状态栏将文本 Add Entry 隐藏起来了 最终我们会修复这个问题的
So it looks like our component is working.
看来我们的组件能正常运行了
So let's go ahead and just test one more thing.
再测试一项功能
What I want to do here is instead of having AddEntry,
我们不再输出 Add Entry
so we can delete text.
删掉这个文本
Let's go ahead and show one of the icons from
改为显示之前创建的
our getMetricMetaInfo function that we created earlier.
getMetricMetaInfo 函数中的某个图标
So let's invoke this,
调用该函数
let's pass it bike,
传入 bike
just so it has the specific metric.
使其具有具体的指标
And then we will say, I believe it was getIcon.
我记得是 getIcon
Yes. So then we can say getIcon then now what we should see up here is we have the bike.
没错 输入 getIcon() 现在在这里能看到骑车图标了